well yes T Lexi continues to surprise on
the upside with very strong Revenue
growth yet this time around as well with
the top line coming uh up by around 6
and 1 half% on a sequential basis ahead
of Street expectations The Profit after
tax also came in higher than expectation
at 185 cross and this is the growth of
15% on a sequential basis the company
has been reporting industry-leading
margins and yet again they have done
that because the ebbit margins stand at
305% and this compares to the other
companies where the average is anywhere
between uh 15 to 20 25% so there is a
definite uh you know upside when it
comes to the margins for uh TTI lexc and
this time around as well the margins
have come in better than expectation the
street was expecting a number of around
29% it has come in at 30 and a half% the
company said that the growth was
primarily volume Leed and has been broad
across all verticals they've added
around 771 employees this quarter which
is double of what they did last quarter
and that tells you that the company is
quite optimistic and confident about the
demand environment attrition has also
slowed down which is another positive
attrition has come down to 19% versus
211% earlier and if you look at the
various verticals it is system
integration and support that really grew
around 20% quarter on quarter leading
the growth the stock has been fairly
resilient versus other other it
companies because the business of Tata
is slightly different they're also more
dependent on the automotive uh business
which has been on an upswing and EV
business is something which also augers
well for the the company and overall if
you look at the margin profile plus
other levers they stand to benefit more
than the other it companies and that's
the reason the stock has been fairly
resilient